(416) 886-9984

eugene@michasiw.com

Toronto, ON

Profile

I am a Front-end Developer with six years of marketing experience in the non-profit sector. With this background, I have had the opportunity to build a broad toolkit of creative and technical skills, including graphic design, email marketing, digital ads, video production, copywriting and everything in-between. In the spring of 2019, I decided to focus my career on the part of my toolkit that I loved the most - web development.

While I have years of experience working with HTML and CSS on corporate Wordpress and Drupal websites, I attended HackerYou's Web Development Bootcamp to learn modern best-practices, web accessibility, JavaScript, jQuery and React. My broad base of experience and recent education make me an ideal candidate for any organization.

Skills

E	1	Н	Т	М	L5
J		1 1		1.1	$_{-}$

♦ VS Code

₹ CSS3

G Firebase

Sass

Wordpress

JavaScript

Drupal

iQuery

■ UI/UX Design

React

Adobe CC

♣ APIs

Email Marketing

git Git

Online Fundraising

GitHub

Links

Portfolio

https://michasiw.com

https://github.com/eugenefm

https://medium.com/@eugenefm

Experience

Capitalize for Kids

Director of Marketing Jan 2018 - Apr 2019 Marketing Manager May 2016 - Dec 2017

I joined Capitalize for Kids to help transform a fundraising event into a full-scale charitable organization. I directed the organization's marketing strategy while managing vendors, freelancers, and pro-bono partners to execute on our plan.

- · Managed all marketing and communications for one of Canada's most important capital markets conferences - an event that raised \$1.5 million for charity in 2018.
- Co-founded the Bay Street Games an event that raised over \$230,000 in 2019.
- · Launched a podcast featuring interviews with business leaders like Michele Romanow, Bruce Croxon and Paul Desmarais III.
- Led the redesign of the organization's website and was responsible for all updates.

Jack.org

Marketing and Communications Lead May 2013 - Apr 2016

I managed all marketing and communications activities at Jack.org. My day to day tasks included maintaining their website and fundraising microsites, producing email campaigns, managing their social media channels, designing promotional materials, and producing digital content.

- · Directed a complete rebranding of the organization in partnership with a pro-bono agency.
- · Launched online fundraising at Jack.org and helped raise \$250,000 (200% of Goal) at their first fundraising event.
- · Supported the launch of the student chapters program and grew it to 100+ campus chapters with 1,000+ members.
- Helped grow total revenue from \$600,000 to \$1.5 million in three years.

Education

Queen's University

Bachelor of Arts, Honours, Film and Media Sep 2009 - Apr 2013

HackerYou

Web Development Bootcamp Apr - Jun 2019